Philip Singer Papers
Philip Singer Papers
- Research files
  - Bee therapies
    - Bees, Flint, 07/24/1995; singer_p_0482; label on container reads, "Bach for eval after being on stings are [illegible], [illegible] wheelchair [illegible]"; Hi8; running time 120:00 (Box 48)
    - M. WIlls, Bonnie talk; Dr. Waite Bee/MS, singer_p_0218; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 42)
  - Behavioral sciences, McCandless, F.D., 1961-1966 (Box 9)
  - The Beneficial Plant Research Association, Weil, Andrew, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Blanche
    - Blanche Demo, UP Infirmary Manila, 1984/03/08; singer_p_0777; label on tape reads, "J.B. - 3 Diabetics - Drs. Palapay-Caraguay-Damian-Capul"; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Oversize 3)
    - Blanche Demo, UP Infirmary Manila, 1984/03/08; singer_p_0778; label on tape reads, "J.B. - 3 Diabetics - Drs. Palapay-Caraguay-Damian-Capul"; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Oversize 3)
    - Blanche Demo: U.P. Infirmary [original], 1984/03/08; singer_p_0687; text on case reads, "JB - 3 diabetes; Drs. Paladay, Caraguay, Damian, Capul"; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Oversize 2)
    - Blanche Life Health, 1973; singer_p_0819; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Box 49)
    - Blanche: Radio WBRB Interview with Philip Singer re: Blanche, 1980/06/15; singer_p_0689; Audio cassette; running time 120:00 (Oversize 2)
  - Body/Mind/Spirit, 1991-1994 (Box 9)
  - Brahmin temple, "Model of a Brahmin Temple," Immanuel M. Casanowicz, 1912 (Box 9)
  - Cancer prevention, 1981-1982 (Box 9)
  - Cannabis, "Mississippi-Grown Marihuana-cannabis sativa Cultivation and Observed Morphological Variations", 1973 (Box 9)
  - Castaneda, undated (Box 9)
  - Castaneda, Carlos, The Castaneda Trilogy as Literature and Anthropology, 1977 (Box 9)
  - Censorship and obscenity, "I am curious" film, 1969 (Box 9)
  - Charisma, notes on, 1965 (Box 9)
  - Charisma, notes on, 1961-1963 (Box 23)
  - Chiropractor, McTimoney Chiropractic School, 1992 (Box 9)
  - Church and healing
    - Comp health, undated (Box 9)
    - Great Faith Ministry, 1996 (Box 9)
    - Maryle Bone, log, 1990-1991 (Box 9)
  - Clitoridectomy
    - A Cruel Ritual: Clitoridectomy, singer_p_1245; set in Africa and Britain; DVD; running time 40:00 (Oversize 6)
    - Clitoridectomy, KOK On, singer_p_0759; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Oversize 3)
    - Clitoridectomy: Female Genital Mutilation, Barbara Walters 20/20 Special, 1997/06/20; singer_p_1238; model from Somalia speaks out; DVD; running time 24:00 (Oversize 6)
    - Female Circumcision, singer_p_1244; BBC program, "40 Minutes"; DVD; running time 40:00 (Oversize 6)
  - Coma, See also Right-to-die
    - Clippings, 1991 (Box 9)
    - Right-to-die court cases, 1989 (Box 9)
    - Right-to-die court cases, 1989 (Box 23)
    - Recordings
      - Coma, 1988; singer_p_0127; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 35)
        Contains clips regarding comas. Itemized label reads: "Eric Smith, Coma (1988)," "Frontline - Nancy Crezan (60:00)," "Eric Smith V - Coma Round Table ," "Life Begins at 80 (23:00, 1986)."
      - Coma, 1990/03/02; singer_p_1288; text on disc reads, "Kelly and Co-Dtr, Jayne Hoskin / panel right to life ethics"; DVD; running time 60:00 (Oversize 6)
      - Coma: Irreversible Coma, singer_p_0126; VHS; running time 20:00 (Box 35)
      - Irreversible Coma, singer_p_0128; VHS; running time 13:00 (Box 35)
      - Irreversible Coma, singer_p_1291; DVD; running time 15:00 (Oversize 6)
      - Right to Die, "Let My Daughter Die," Frontline, 1988/02/28; singer_p_0708; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Oversize 3)
  - Complementary and conventional treatments, House of Lords (UK) official report, 1990 (Box 9)
  - Conference on Medicine and Anthropology, 1961 (Box 9)
  - Criminal insanity, Daniel De Sole, 1988-1992 (Box 9)
  - Cuba
    - Cuba, singer_p_1444; DVD; running time 49:00 (Box 55)
    - Cuba (Raw) Santoria (1 of 2), 2000; singer_p_1435; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 55)
    - Cuba #1, 2000; singer_p_1546; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 43)
    - Cuba #2, 2000/07/25; singer_p_1547; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 43)
    - Cuba #3, 2000/07/26; singer_p_1548; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 43)
  - Cupping, 1999; articles and websites (Box 10)
  - Czechoslovakia and Calabria, Italy, 1986-1988 (Box 10)
  - Danville, Kentucky
    - Danville, Kentucky #1, 2000; singer_p_1543; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 43)
    - Danville, Kentucky #2, 2000; singer_p_1544; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 43)
    - Danville, Kentucky #3, 2000; singer_p_1545; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 43)
  - Death
    - Clippings, 2011-2014 (Box 10)
    - "The Heroics of Everyday Life: A Theorist of Death Confronts His Own End," Psychology Today, Apr 1974 (Box 10)
    - Notes, undated (Box 10)
    - Recordings
      - Dying: Wiseman, singer_p_0131; most likely Frederick documentary "Near Death" that documents an intensive care unit at Boston's Beth Israel Hospital; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 35)
  - Depression, 2006-2007; See also Kahlo, Frida (Box 10)
  - DeSole, Daniel
    - Dan DeSole, Suicide, Contemplating Suicide, Summary, Living Well #6, 2007; singer_p_1084; DVD; running time 46:00 (Oversize 5)
    - Dan DeSole, Suicide, Dread, Lethargy, Dogs #5, 2007; singer_p_1083; DVD; running time 46:00 (Oversize 5)
    - Dan[iel DeSole], 12/17/2005; singer_p_0407; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 46)
    - Dan[iel DeSole] Interview, singer_p_0440; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 46)
    - Daniel DeSole #1, 12/01/2007; singer_p_0377; label on tape reads, "Suicide attempt"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
    - Daniel DeSole #1, 12/16/2005; singer_p_0382; label on tape reads, "Re: Carl"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
    - Daniel DeSole #2, 12/01/2007; singer_p_0378; label on tape reads, "Lethargy, Sullivan County, NY"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
    - Daniel DeSole #2, 12/17/2005; singer_p_0383; label on tape reads, "Criticism"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
    - Daniel DeSole #3, 12/02/2007; singer_p_0379; label on tape reads, "Sullivan County, NY"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
    - Daniel DeSole #4, 12/02/2007; singer_p_0380; label on tape reads, "Sullivan County, NY"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
    - Daniel DeSole #4, 12/18/2005; singer_p_0384; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
    - Daniel DeSole #5, 12/04/2007; singer_p_0381; label on tape reads, "Suicide - living - what for?, final statement"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
    - Daniel DeSole #5, 12/18/2005; singer_p_0385; label on tape reads, "Harm reduction"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
    - Daniel DeSole #6, 12/07/2007; singer_p_0386; label on tape reads, "suicide"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
    - Daniel DeSole interview #1, 08/18/1998; singer_p_0373; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
    - Daniel DeSole interview #2, 08/20/1998; singer_p_0374; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
    - Daniel DeSole interview #3, 08/18/1998; singer_p_0375; label on tape reads, "Gail - Schizo, [illegible] lunch, Int/Sidney/Interview Dan - Pt.1"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
    - Daniel DeSole interview #4, 08/18/1998; singer_p_0376; label on tape reads, "Interview, continued, intake"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
    - [Daniel] DeSole, 08/18/1998; singer_p_0425; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 46)
    - DeSole, Daniel / Philip Singer, singer_p_0841; Audio cassette; running time 60:00 (Box 50)
    - DeSole, Daniel, "Rational Suicide", 2007/12/03; singer_p_1088; label reads, "Sauferties, NY, December 3, 07"; DVD; running time 58:00 (Oversize 5)
    - DeSole/VA Monologue, Kerouac at Tony's Bar, singer_p_0552; Audio cassette; running time 60:00 (Oversize 1)
  - Dowsing
    - American Society of Dowsers, 1981 (Box 10)
    - Articles, 1968; 1981-1989 (Box 10)
    - Clippings, 1981-1984 (Box 10)
    - "The Divining Rod," Rossiter W. Raymond, Jan 1885 (Box 10)
    - General, 1981-1992 (Box 10)
    - "A History of Water Witching," Smithsonian, 1957 (Box 10)
    - "Is Science Catching Up with Magic?" Anthropology, 1975 (Box 10)
    - Kubelbeck, 1978-1983 (Box 10)
    - "Plain and Fancy Shooting with the Witches," Country Journal, Aug 1981 (Box 11)
    - Science of, 1975-1988 (Box 11)
    - Recordings
      - Dowsing, singer_p_0569; label on tape reads, "4 bears, discussion with Indian [planter?] re: one year delay on $30,000 repair job on lodge's leaking roof"; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Oversize 1)
      - "Dowsing", September 25, 1987; singer_p_0130; "20/20" special on Dowsing that aired on September 25, 1987; VHS; running time 60:00 (Box 35)
      - Water Dowsing in Middle America: Water Witching, singer_p_1076; DVD; running time 19:00 (Oversize 5)
  - Dying, "The Bitter End," podcast transcript, Radio Lab, 2013 (Box 11)
  - Egadi, Sicily, 1995 (Box 11)
  - El Nino Fidencio, 1991, 2004; 2004 (Box 59)
  - Endangered species, 2009-2016 (Box 11)
  - Ethics, human nature, medical progress, Hastings Center Report, 1990 (Box 11)
  - Evolution
    - Evolution, 2009/10/12; singer_p_1354; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 53)
    - Evolution, 2009/10/12; singer_p_1355; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 53)
    - Evolution (disc 3), singer_p_1345; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 53)
  - Exorcism
    - Exorcism Follow Up, singer_p_1356; DVD; running time 120:00 (Box 53)
    - Exorcism: 20/20 Special, 1991; singer_p_1414; handwritten text on disc reads, "See reinventing shamanism"; DVD; running time 28:00 (Box 55)
      Recording of the ABC news program 20/20 regarding exorcism. It features an exorcism by Catholic Priest James LeBar. Also includes an exorcism follow up with an interview with Philip Singer.
  - Faith-based healing, 1981-1991; clippings (Box 23)
  - False face, Jacob Thomas, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
  - Families, Black
    - Manuscript material, 1964 (Box 11)
    - Recordings
      - DTR Mission, singer_p_0133; label reads, "Black culture", includes a racial epithet, dubbed from 8mm; VHS; running time 60:00 (Box 35)
      - DTR Mission, singer_p_0134; label reads, "Black culture", includes a racial epithet, dubbed from 8mm, includes note to Singer from John De Carlo; VHS; running time 60:00 (Box 35)
      - DTR. Mission, Interviews "Black" (2 of 2), 1990; singer_p_0855; title also includes a racial epithet; Hi8; running time 120:00 (Box 50)
  - Folk medicine
    - Creole and Doctor Medicine, William R. Aho and Kimlan Minott, Social Science and Medicine, 1977 (Box 11)
    - The Image of the African Medicine Man, W.G. Jilek, 1967 (Box 11)
    - "The Other Kind of Doctor: Conjure and Magic in Black American Folk Medicine," Bruce Jackson, undated (Box 23)
  - Fordham University, Fourth Conference on East Indians, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Fraud
    - General, 1971-1988 (Box 11)
    - India, 1989-1992 (Box 11)
    - "The Methodological Significance of the Lying Informant," Frank A. Salamone, 1975 (Box 11)
    - Wanita Wannamaker, 1986 (Box 11)
  - Get rich quick schemes, 2003; email frauds (Box 11)
  - Giglio Feasts
    - Research material, 2007 (Box 11)
    - Recordings
      - Giglio, singer_p_1272; DVD; running time 115:00 (Oversize 6)
        Text on case reads: "NOLA - bread - capo, interviews - boy and breakfast, bands, cassato - NOLA visitor - new song from NOLA. Bread blessing / distribution. Brooklyn bridge. Cleaning up - interviews with Chinese, Anthony Palma - capo, Giglio prep."
      - Giglio, singer_p_1273; DVD; running time 115:00 (Oversize 6)
      - Giglio, singer_p_1274; DVD; running time 115:00 (Oversize 6)
        Text on disc reads, "Interviews with Cassato, etc., child lift"; text on case reads, "Prep to raise Giglio, children, interview with Cassato, interviews [regarding] meaning of Giglio, men prep."
      - Giglio 1-2 Williamsburg, 2000; singer_p_1460; DVD; running time 115:00 (Box 55)
      - Giglio 3 and 4, singer_p_1443; handwritten label on disc reads, "lift and bread"; DVD; running time 110:00 (Box 55)
      - Giglio 5 and 6, singer_p_1442; handwritten label on disc reads, "Kid lift, prep meeting, ints, cassato interview"; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 55)
      - [Giglio] #1, singer_p_1536; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 43)
      - [Giglio] #2 Kids Lift, singer_p_1537; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 43)
      - [Giglio] #3 Bread Sale, singer_p_1538; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 43)
      - [Giglio] #4 Sunday Lift, singer_p_1539; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 43)
      - [Giglio] #5 Kids Tugs, singer_p_1540; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 43)
      - Giglio #7 Discussion of Nola vs Brooklyn, singer_p_1416; DVD; running time 33:00 (Box 55)
      - [Giglio] Brooklyn Interviews, singer_p_1542; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 43)
      - Giglio 1st Day, 2000; singer_p_1459; DVD; running time 115:00 (Box 55)
      - Nola, singer_p_1398; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 55)
      - NOLA #1, Interview, 01/08/2000; singer_p_0401; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 46)
      - NOLA Giglio, 2000/01/02; singer_p_1410; handwrittend text on disc reads, "Luigi house, family disc., old rai videos"; DVD; running time 20:00 (Box 55)
      - Nola Giglio, 2000; singer_p_1110; label on disc reads, "Preparations - artists background, comparing Brooklyn, Bronx and Nola"; DVD; running time 60:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Nola Giglio, singer_p_1311; DVD; running time 90:00 (Oversize 6)
        Text on case reads: "Giglio workplace: sculpture models [London, Moscow, Paris, Rome, etc.], artists, translator, Nola - Brooklyn composed by Luigi, apprentice artists; Nola location; Luigi's home [looking at giglio videos], family discuss Giglio in the blood."
      - Nola Giglio Rai Due, singer_p_1312; DVD; running time 31:00 (Oversize 6)
      - Nola Giglio Rai II, singer_p_1315; DVD; running time 30:00 (Oversize 6)
      - Nola: Storia Arte Tradizione Della Citta Dei Gigli, singer_p_1109; DVD; running time 60:00 (Oversize 5)
  - Global warming
    - An Inconvenient Truth, singer_p_1326; plus update evidence; DVD; running time 90:00 (Oversize 6)
    - An Inconvenient Truth, singer_p_1327; includes update and director voice over; DVD; running time 90:00 (Oversize 6)
  - Grant, Walter Vinson, Jr.
    - Reverend Grant at Cabo, 1982/09/20; singer_p_0786; Audio cassette; running time 120:00 (Oversize 3)
    - Reverend Grant Interview and Skeptical inquiry, singer_p_0511; label continues, "use of my article 'Justifies Healing'; Audio cassette; running time 60:00 (Oversize 1)
    - Reverend Grant Interview Regarding OS/PAK Article; Cisneros Interview, singer_p_0816; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Box 49)
  - Guyana
    - "Amerindian Attitudes and Integration," Andrew Sanders, 1968 (Box 23)
    - Shri Maha Kali Devi Mandis, Inc., 1998-2003 (Box 11)
    - Witchcraft, 1987-1990 (Box 11)
    - Recordings
      - [Guyana - Lamb] Timemri - Preparation, singer_p_1471; Hi8; running time 120:00 (Box 56)
      - [Guyana - Lamb] Kali Mai Puja (2), singer_p_1462; Hi8; running time 120:00 (Box 50)
      - [Guyana - Lamb] Kali Mai Puja (3), singer_p_1463; Hi8; running time 120:00 (Box 50)
      - [Guyana - Lamb] Kali Mai Puja (4), singer_p_1464; Hi8; running time 120:00 (Box 50)
      - [Guyana - Lamb] Kali Mai Puja (5), singer_p_1465; Hi8; running time 120:00 (Box 50)
      - [Guyana - Lamb] Kali Mai Puja (6), singer_p_1466; Hi8; running time 120:00 (Box 50)
      - [Guyana - Lamb] Kali Mai Puja (7), singer_p_1467; handwritten text on case reads, "Sunday - last day"; Hi8; running time 120:00 (Box 56)
      - [Guyana - Lamb] Kali Mai Puja (8), singer_p_1468; Hi8; running time 120:00 (Box 56)
      - [Guyana - Lamb] Kali Mai Puja (9), singer_p_1469; Hi8; running time 120:00 (Box 56)
      - [Guyana - Lamb] Kali Mai Puja (10), singer_p_1470; Hi8; running time 120:00 (Box 56)
      - [Guyana 1990] [Untitled], 1998/02/02; singer_p_1493; includes handwritten note that reads, "First part of tape about 5 minutes bad sound - towards the end you get Sidney - fat guy who keeps dozing off has 'pickwickian syndrome'"; VHS: VHS-C; running time 20:00 (Box 57)
      - [Guyana 1990] [Untitled], 1998/02/04; singer_p_1494; VHS: VHS-C; running time 30:00 (Box 57)
      - [Guyana 1990] #1 First Day, 1990/01/12; singer_p_1487; Hi8; running time 120:00 (Box 57)
      - [Guyana 1990] #2 Second Day, 1990/01/13; singer_p_1488; Hi8; running time 120:00 (Box 57)
      - [Guyana 1990] #3 Lash, Goats, Docks, Healing, 1990/01/14; singer_p_1489; Hi8; running time 120:00 (Box 57)
      - [Guyana 1990] #4 Last Night Cargum, 1990/01/15; singer_p_1490; Hi8; running time 120:00 (Box 57)
      - [Guyana 1990] 01/14/1998, 1998/01/14; singer_p_1492; VHS: VHS-C; running time 20:00 (Box 57)
      - [Guyana 1990] Patient #2, 1998/01/28; singer_p_1491; VHS: VHS-C; running time 30:00 (Box 57)
      - Jamsie / Judson CTR, 10/30/1989; singer_p_0473; Hi8; running time 120:00 (Box 48)
      - Jamsie Naidu, Kali Mai Therapy, Guyana Radio (Part 3 of 4), 1977; singer_p_1314; CD; running time 30:00 (Oversize 6)
      - Jamsie Naidu In Toronto, Home of Pearl, 1997/01/12; singer_p_1549; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 43)
      - JN Healing Lecture to MSU Medical School, singer_p_0538; Audio cassette; running time 120:00 (Oversize 1)
      - Kali Mai Jamsie, singer_p_0611; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Oversize 2)
      - Kali Mai Rituals, Anthropologists and Informants, Whose Truths?, singer_p_0056; VHS; running time 43:00 (Box 29)
      - Kali Mai: Hail Mother Kali, singer_p_0152; VHS; running time 60:00 (Box 37)
      - Kali Mai: J. Naidu Comment on Kali Films, singer_p_0159; VHS; running time 60:00 (Box 37)
      - Kali Mai: She Who is God Prayers to Kali Mai, singer_p_0150; label on case reads, "Pujari Jamsie Naidu from Guyana, South America Prays, Chants and Drums to the Divine Mother, Kali Mai"; VHS; running time 41:35 (Box 36)
      - Kali Mai: She Who is God Prayers to Kali Mai, singer_p_0151; label on case reads, "Pujari Jamsie Naidu from Guyana, South America Prays, Chants and Drums to the Divine Mother, Kali Mai"; VHS; running time 41:35 (Box 37)
      - Kali Music, singer_p_0523; label on tape reads, "First beginnings to understand Kali Mai, no 'jollification' but 'Kali Music, the 'work''"; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Oversize 1)
      - Kali: Day 2 of 3-Day, 1999/12/01; singer_p_1287; text on disc reads, "Ordinary reality, healing"; DVD; running time 60:00 (Oversize 6)
  - Hale clinic, 1991 (Box 23)
  - Hallucination, "The Historical Background of the Concept of Hallucination," Theodore R. Sarbin and Joseph B. Juhasz, undated (Box 11)
  - Hare Krishna
    - Jesus freaks, interview with followers, undated (Box 12)
    - Recordings
      - Hare Krishna, Stan Bernstein of Ann Arbor on Hare Krishna Movement, 1971/02/20; singer_p_0557; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Oversize 1)
      - Hare Krishna, Stan Bernstein on, singer_p_0825; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Box 49)
      - Hare Krishna, Swami Satswarupa, Hindu C + P Interview showing Unilateral Transference, singer_p_0556; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Oversize 1)
  - Herbalism and herbal practice, undated (Box 12)
  - Hermetic Healing in Italy: The Magical Therapeutic Brotherhood of Myriam, Dana Lloyd Thomas, 1995 (Box 12)
  - Hinduism
    - Hindu C and P, Drs. Reddi and Desai, 1975/07/23; singer_p_0707; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Oversize 3)
    - Hindu C and P, Swami Satswarupa, Hare Krishna, 1974/10/22; singer_p_0706; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Oversize 3)
    - Hindu C and P, Meditation, Shiva Jyole, 1974; singer_p_0711; WJR radio show; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Oversize 3)
    - "Hindu Concept of Mind... Phenomenal Absolute and Dream", singer_p_0505; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Oversize 1)
    - Hindu Loaves and Fishes, singer_p_0939; DVD; running time 20:00 (Oversize 4)
    - Hindu Loaves and Fishes, singer_p_0940; DVD; running time 20:00 (Oversize 4)
    - Hindu Loaves and Fishes, singer_p_0941; DVD; running time 20:00 (Oversize 4)
  - Hispanic communities, "Detroit's Hidden Hispanic Community", June 1983 (Box 12)
  - Homepathy, 1993; clipping and notes (Box 12)
  - Hypnosis
    - Loren Parks, 1981-1982 (Box 12)
    - Recordings
      - American Society of Clinical Hypnosis, singer_p_0811; label on cassette reads, "Fromm - Hypnotherapy, Lazar - Utilization Techniques, Hershoman - Smoking"; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Box 49)
      - Clinical Hypnosis Workshop in Chicago, 1980/10/16; singer_p_0650; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Oversize 2)
      - Dissociation in Hypnosis & Psychothera, Pt. 1, 1981; singer_p_0641; label on tape reads, "American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1981 Annual Convention January 3-8, Toronto"; Audio cassette; running time 60:00 (Oversize 2)
      - Dissociation in Hypnosis and Psychothera, Pt. 2, American Association for the Advancement of Science 1981 Annual Convention January 3-8, Toronto, singer_p_0584; Audio cassette; running time 60:00 (Oversize 1)
      - Erickson Milton Hypnosis, 2000/01/02; singer_p_1411; DVD; running time 57:00 (Box 55)
      - Hypnosis, singer_p_0620; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Oversize 2)
      - Hypnosis, Difficult Patient, Techniques, singer_p_0540; Audio cassette; running time 60:00 (Oversize 1)
      - Hypnosis, Taking History Ideas of Hypnosis, Smoking, Weight, 10/19/1976; singer_p_0541; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Oversize 1)
      - Hypnosis "Well of Mind", singer_p_0610; Audio cassette; running time 60:00 (Oversize 2)
      - Hypnosis and Management of Pain (Dr. Brasher), singer_p_0704; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Oversize 3)
      - Hypnosis for Pain Control, singer_p_0645; label on case reads, "Strategies for pain control and physical discomfort, typical office scenario for dealing with patients in pain"; Audio cassette; running time 60:00 (Oversize 2)
      - Hypnosis: Blood and Hypnosis; Restore with Hypnosis, singer_p_0782; other text appears on tape, but are illegible; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Oversize 3)
      - Hypno-therapy, Chavez, Induction Procedures, singer_p_0663; label on tape reads, "Side I - Pt. I - Health Hypnosis, Side II - Pt. II - Induction Procedures"; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Oversize 2)
      - Hypnotherapeutic Approaches to Chronic Pain Management, singer_p_0581; Audio cassette; running time 60:00 (Oversize 1)
      - Hypnotherapeutic Approaches to Chronic Pain Management, singer_p_0662; label on tape reads, "Anesthesia induction - hypnosis and various pain sits - cancer ob/gyn"; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Oversize 2)
      - Hypnotic Induction: Concepts and Procedures, singer_p_0582; Audio cassette; running time 60:00 (Oversize 1)
      - Hypnotic Realities, singer_p_0583; Audio cassette; running time 60:00 (Oversize 1)
        The tape label offers a description of contents. It reads, "Side 1: Dr. Rossi discusses the utilization theory of hypnotic suggestion and indirect forms of suggestion. Dr. Erickson's first session in the trance training of Dr. S. Side 2: Dr. Rossi introduces Dr. Erickson's second session in the trance training of Dr. S. Dr. Erickson's second session in the trance training of Dr. S. Dr. Rossi discusses Dr. Erickson's approaches to trance induction."
      - Hypnotic Strategies / Talking in Trance, singer_p_0718; Audio cassette; running time 60:00 (Oversize 3)
      - Hypnotherapeutic Approaches to Chronic Pain Management, singer_p_0581; Audio cassette; running time 60:00 (Oversize 1)
      - Hypnotherapeutic Approaches to Chronic Pain Management, singer_p_0662; label on tape reads, "Anesthesia induction - hypnosis and various pain sits - cancer ob/gyn"; Audio cassette; running time 90:00 (Oversize 2)
      - Hypnotic Induction: Concepts and Procedures, singer_p_0582; Audio cassette; running time 60:00 (Oversize 1)
      - Hypnotic Realities, singer_p_0583; Audio cassette; running time 60:00 (Oversize 1)